<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Mehring's Page]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Mehring's Page]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/mehring-s-page/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 00:50:48 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/mehring-s-page/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Welcome!</h1><p>Glad you made it here and I hope you find the site -- and the ideas -- beneficial. Feel free to look around and contact me anytime.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/mehring-s-page/welcome/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a4ba3219-79cb-4682-8051-4ad248e6a2c1</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 00:30:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Teaching Philosophy]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Teaching Philosophy</h1><p>My philosophy has always been based on teaching methods that integrate technologies to enhance and expand the second language learning environment in ways unobtainable by traditional methods. Conole (2004) expressed it perfectly when he said, there is a lapse between what is proposed and the actual use of technology in the classroom; there is minimal evidence that fundamental change in education has taken place as a result of the application of emerging technologies. Teachers need to create environments and experiences where students come together, either face-to-face or online, to discover and construct new learning, become members of the community of learners, and solve problems (Barr & Tagg, 1995). In this new ecological learning environment, students learn to be active learners and constructors of their knowledge, developing and creating entire frameworks of new knowledge through collaborative, authentic use of students’ previous knowledge. In keeping with van Lier’s (2000) principles of ecological education, I am continually looking for new ways of teaching, integrating technology into learning, and researching education in order to expand the quality of the learner’s environment both inside and outside the classroom. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/mehring-s-page/teaching-philosophy/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a38a36dc-6478-453b-b135-cb4ceaaa15a0</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 00:49:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Apps]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Apps</h1><p>With the dramatic increase in smart devices Apps have become a great learning tool that are easy to set up and use both in-class and for independent study. There are so many Apps, both free and for purchase, I have chosen to only focus on Apps I regularly use in my classes. When I look at an App, price and usability are major considerations. I do not want to overburden students with buying too many Apps. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/mehring-s-page/apps/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">275ad228-0e89-4a01-a6dd-e455f12d6e08</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 09:42:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Flipped Classroom ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Flipped Classroom </h1><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/cf14c154ff1246bd3bc19ac1110e4f1fbef17664.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/mehring-s-page/flipped-classroom/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ab48c127-6208-481a-a4a8-6a08e6ead0fe</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2016 09:34:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>